<resources>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="app_name">Skin Lesion</string>
    <string name="gallerybtn">Gallery</string>
    <string name="camerabtn">Camera</string>
    <string name="title">This app can be used to detect different types of Skin Lesions From image
        just click the image or select directly from the gallery</string>


    <string name="melanocytic_navi_h">Melanocytic nevus</string>
    <string name="melanocytic_navi">Melanocytic nevi are benign neoplasms or
        hamartomas composed of melanocytes, the pigment-producing cells that constitutively colonize the epidermis.
        Melanocytes are derived from the neural crest and migrate during embryogenesis to selected ectodermal
        sites (primarily the skin and the CNS), but also to the eyes and the ears. Ectopic melanocytes have
        been identified at autopsy in the gastrointestinal and genitourinary tracts. Congenital melanocytic
        nevi are thought to represent an anomaly in embryogenesis and, as such, could be
        considered, at least in a sense, malformations or hamartomas.
        In contrast, most acquired melanocytic nevi are considered benign neoplasms.
        Compare the images below. Melanocytic nevi occur in all mammalian species and
        are especially common in humans, dogs, and horses.
    </string>

    <string name="Melanoma_h">Melanoma</string>
    <string name="Melanoma">Melanoma, also redundantly known as malignant melanoma,
        is a type of skin cancer that develops from the pigment-producing cells known
        as melanocytes. Melanomas typically occur in the skin but may rarely occur in
        the mouth, intestines or eye (uveal melanoma).
    </string>


    <string name="Benign_keratosis_like_lesions_h">Benign keratosis like lesions</string>
    <string name="Benign_keratosis_like_lesions">Seborrheic keratoses are noncancerous (benign)
        skin growths that some people develop as they age. They often appear on the back or
        chest, but can occur on any part of the body. Seborrheic keratoses grow slowly,
        in groups or singly. Most people will develop at least one seborrheic keratosis
        during their lifetime.

        The appearance of seborrheic keratoses can vary widely.
        They may be light tan to brown or black. The most common
        texture is rough, with a bumpy, grainy surface that crumbles easily.
        However, they also may be smooth and waxy. They usually look like they\'ve
        been stuck onto the skin. While some are tiny, others grow larger
        than 3 cm in diameter.
    </string>


    <string name="Basal_cell_carcinoma_h">Basal cell carcinoma</string>
    <string name="Basal_cell_carcinoma">
        Basal cell carcinoma is a type of skin cancer. Basal cell carcinoma begins
        in the basal cells — a type of cell within the skin that produces new skin
        cells as old ones die off.

        Basal cell carcinoma often appears as a slightly transparent bump
        on the skin, though it can take other forms. Basal cell carcinoma
        occurs most often on areas of the skin that are exposed to the sun,
        such as your head and neck.

        Most basal cell carcinomas are thought to be caused by long-term exposure
        to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from sunlight.
    </string>


    <string name="Actinic_keratoses_h">Actinic keratoses</string>
    <string name="Actinic_keratoses">
        An actinic keratosis (ak-TIN-ik ker-uh-TOE-sis) is a rough, scaly patch
        on the skin that develops from years of sun exposure.
        It\'s often found on the face, lips, ears, forearms, scalp, neck or back of the hands.

        Also known as a solar keratosis, an actinic keratosis grows slowly
        and usually first appears in people over 40. You can reduce your
        risk of this skin condition by minimizing your sun exposure and
        protecting your skin from ultraviolet (UV) rays.

        Left untreated, the risk of actinic keratoses turning
        into a type of skin cancer called squamous cell carcinoma is about 5% to 10%
    </string>


    <string name="Vascular_lesions_h">Vascular lesions</string>
    <string name="Vascular_lesions">Vascular lesions are relatively common abnormalities
        of the skin and underlying tissues, more commonly known as birthmarks. There are
        three major categories of vascular lesions: Hemangiomas, Vascular Malformations,
        and Pyogenic Granulomas. While these birthmarks can look similar at times,
        they each vary in terms of origin and necessary treatment.
    </string>


    <string name="Dermatofibroma_h">Dermatofibroma</string>
    <string name="Dermatofibroma">Dermatofibroma (superficial benign fibrous histiocytoma)
        is a common cutaneous nodule of unknown etiology that occurs more often in women.
        Dermatofibroma frequently develops on the extremities (mostly the lower legs)
        and is usually asymptomatic, although pruritus and tenderness can be present.
        It is actually the most common painful skin tumor.
         A number of well-described, histologic subtypes of
        dermatofibroma have been reported. Removal of the tumor
        is usually not typically required unless diagnostic
        uncertainty exists or particularly troubling symptoms are present.</string>


    <string name="name">AMIT KUSHWAHA 20</string>
    <string name="college">Student at K J Somaiya College of Science &amp; Commerce
        Vidyanagar Vidyavihar Mumbai 400 077
    </string>
    <string name="location">Mumbai, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="more">Read more</string>
    <string name="about">About: </string>
    <string name="about_b">Developer &amp; programmer</string>
    <string name="about_b2">A good software developer with decent problem solving skills\nhard working and creative.</string>
    <string name="about_app_h">About Application:</string>
    <string name="about_app">This app can be used to detect \ncommon Lesion types including\ncancer this app is build using \nconvolution neural network \nin TensorFlow Framework which
        \nis further integrated in Android \nwith elegant and user \nfriendly UI. </string>
    <string name="ver">Version 1.0.0</string>
    <string name="more1">More</string>

    <string name="hows1">1. This is the main page of the Application here you have
to choose image either from gallery of click with camera. You can click on the hamburger icon on the top left corner to acesses the
        navigation drawer. Also there is 3 dots on top right corner which you can click and choose exit to exit the app.</string>
    <string name="hows2">2. On this screen the report will be shown after choosing the image if you want you can read more about the particular Skin lesion by clicking on read more
    or else you can choose another image for detection.\nNote: Home icon on the toolbar is used to directly navigate to
        the home screen or you can also use back button or gesture of you phone to navigate.</string>
    <string name="hows3">3. This is the navigation drawer of the screen which contains different options as follows:\n
           a. "Home" to navigate on home screen.\n
           b. "How To Use" This section demonstrates how to use \tthis application.\n
           c. "About me" This section has short introduction about \tme along which contact details.\n
           d. "Share this App" This option is used to share the link of \tthis Application.
    </string>
    <string name="how4">4. This is Lesion Types section where you can read about different Skin lesions and also there is read more button
    on each subsection which can be used to read more about particular lesion on the Internet.</string>

    <string name="how5">5. This is about me section here you will find some information about me also 4 buttons i.e email, linkdin, github, twitter.
        which will redirect you to respective social media or service.</string>

    <string name="about_t">About Me</string>
    <string name="report_t">Report</string>
    <string name="hows_t">How To Use</string>
    <string name="les_t">Lesion Types</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
</resources>